Register of the Joan Beecher Eichrodt collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Sound Recordings, 1988-1999 (Boxes 34-40)
  - Miscellaneous, 1991-1994, 1996-1997
    - Kennan Institute panel on the ethnic history of the Caucasus, 1991 February 28 (Box-folder 40: 29)
    - Fedor Burlatskiĭ on Abkhazia, South Ossetia and Ingushetia, 1991 November 7 (Box-folder 40: 30)
      Includes a description of negotiations between Azerbaijan and Armenia concerning Nagorno-Karabakh.
    - Nikolaĭ Medvedev on politics, borders, and independence movements in the North Caucasus, 1992 February 18 (Box-folder 40: 31)
    - Khadzhi-Murat Ibragimbeĭli on ethnic conflicts and the history of the North Caucasus, 1993 (Box-folder 40: 32-33)
    - Ramazan Abdulatipov and Stepanov on conflicts in the North Caucasus, 1993 May 14 (Box-folder 40: 34)
    - Unidentified historian on the history of the Cossacks in the Caucasus, 1993 June 9 (Box-folder 40: 35)
    - Ismail Mussaevich Miziev on languages and archeology of the Caucasus, 1993 July 14 (Box-folder 40: 36)
    - Nikolaĭ Petrov on border disputes in the Caucasus, 1994 May 28 (Box-folder 40: 37)
    - Unidentified man on the history of the Caucasus, 1996 (Box-folder 40: 38)
    - Panel on oil pipelines in Kazakhstan and the Caspian region with [Kasymzhomart?] Tokaev, 1996 (Box-folder 40: 39)
    - Dneprovsk, 1996 (Box-folder 40: 40)
      Interview on the Russian elections with an unidentified man.
    - Panel on economic reform in Kazakhstan, circa 1997 (Box-folder 40: 41)
    - Caspian pipelines, 1997 July 24 and November (Box-folder 40: 42)
      On different projects for exporting Caspian oil.
- Card File, 1990s (Box 41)
  Eichrodt's notes on research materials.
- Floppy Disks, 1986-1988, undated (Box 41)
  Consists of Voice of America working files, arranged in chronological order.
  - 1986 (Box-folder 41: 1-2)
  - 1987 (Box-folder 41: 3-4)
  - 1988 (Box-folder 41: 5-7)
  - undated (Box-folder 41: 8-18)
- Videorecordings, 1990 (Box 41)
  Contains VHS videocassettes from the Democratic Party congress in Moscow.
  - S"ezd demokraticheskoi partii, 1990 May 26-27 (Box-folder 41: 19-20)
- Newspapers, 1989-1997 (Boxes 42-45)
  Incomplete runs, primarily from newspapers in the Caucasus. Grouped by publication location, then ordered alphabetically by title.
  - Abkhazia, 1990-1994
    - Abkhaziia, 1994 (Box 42)
    - Abkhazskiĭ vestnik, 1993 January - 1994 June
    - Alashara, 1990 July-September
    - Bzyb', 1993 August
    - Edinenie: narodnyĭ forum Abkhazii, 1993
    - Gagra, 1993 August 25
    - Kavkaz, 1991 October 13 - December 25
    - Konfederatsiia, 1993 January-August
    - Respublika Abkhaziia, 1993 August
    - Sosryk"u, 1993
    - Svobodnaia Abkhaziia, 1993 July
    - Za nashe otechestvo, 1993 August
  - Adygea, 1992-1993
    - Bol'shevik Kavkaza, 1992 June 19
    - Sovetskaia Adygeia, 1993 July 20
  - Chechnia, 1989-1997
    - Bart, 1992 January
    - Chechnia, 1992 September 11
    - Daĭmokhk, 1995-1996
    - Ekho Chechnii, 1992 September
    - Ekho gor, 1991 February-December
    - Golos Checheno-Ingushetii, 1992 January - 1997 February
    - Golos naroda, 1994 April-August
    - Groznenskiĭ rabochiĭ, 1995 June 15 - December 17
    - Gums, 1993-1995
    - Ichkeriia, 1992 July 4 - 1997 February 8
    - Imam, 1995 January 23
    - Impul's, 1992-1997
    - Informatsionnyĭ vestnik, 1995 August (Box 43)
    - Islamskaia natsiia, 1997 December
    - Kavkazskaia khronika, 1993 May
    - Kavkazskie vesti, 1993 May 31
    - Kavkazskiĭ dom, 1992 April 19
    - Kriminal'nyĭ kolokol, 1995 November
    - Marsho, 1995 May 31 - 1996 May 18
    - Maslaĭat, 1991-1993
    - Nedelia, 1995-1996
    - Nomer odin, 1997
    - Novosti groznogo, 1992-1993
    - Respublika, 1991-1996
    - Sel'skie vesti, 1995 November
    - Soglasie, 1996 March
    - Soldatskoe slovo, 1993 May
    - Spravedlivost', 1990-1996
    - Spravedlivost': Biulleten' checheno-ingushskogo narodnogo fronta sodeĭstviia perestroĭke, 1989 February
    - Svoboda, 1991 September 5 - 1994 December 2
    - Terkiĭst, 1995 April-October
    - Terskaia pravda, 1991 November-December
    - Vast, 1993 May, 1997 January
    - Vozrozhdenie, 1995 April - 1996 January (Box 44)
    - Zashchitnik otechestva, 1996 December
    - Znamia truda, 1992 January 11
  - Dagestan, 1991, 1995-1996
    - Dagestan, 1991 January-March
    - Dagestanskaia pravda, 1996 July 9
    - Novoe delo, 1995 July
    - Zov predkov, 1996 March
  - Ingushetia, 1991-1995
    - Edinstvo, 1993 February
    - Golos Nazrani, 1995 June 24
    - Ingushetiia, 1993-1995
    - Ingushskoe slovo, 1991 December
    - Nazranovets (Na'sarkho), 1991-1992
    - Orstkho, 1991-1995
    - Serdalo, 1992 May 9 - 1995 August 1
    - Vestnik natsional'nogo fronta Ingushetii, 1993 February
    - Zamankho-Sovremennik, 1993
  - Kabardino-Balkariia, 1991-1994
    - Balkarskiĭ forum, 1991, 1993
    - Gazeta iuga, 1994 October
    - Kabardino-Balkarskaia pravda, 1993 July 17
    - Khase, 1994 October 8
    - Nart, 1992 August - 1993 September
    - Respublika, 1994 October
    - Sovetskaia molodezh', 1993 July 16
    - Tere, 1992 August, 1993 March
  - Kazakhstan, 1991-1992
    - S-Demokrat, 1991-1992
  - Krasnodarskiĭ kraĭ, 1993-1996
    - Argumenty i fakty: Kuban', no. 26, 1996 June
    - Golos cherkesa, 1993 May
    - Kazach'i vesti, nos. 21-24, 1996 June-July
    - Krasnodarskie izvestiia, nos. 119-121, 1996 July
    - Kuban' segodnia, no. 33, 1996 July 1
    - Kubanskiĭ kraĭ, no. 10, 1996 June
    - Molodezhnyĭ dom, no. 3, 1995 November (Box 45)
    - Shapsugiia, 1991-1993
    - Vol'naia Kuban, nos. 121 and 123, 1996 July
  - Latvia, 1990
    - Atmoda, 1990 January 2
  - North Ossetia, 1990, 1992-1993
    - Adaemon Tsadis (Narodnyĭ soiuz), 1990 July-September
    - Vestnik, 1992 November - 1993 March
  - Russia, 1990-1997
    - Argumenty i fakty, 1995 October, 1997 January
    - Duma, 1994-1995
    - Grazhdanskoe dostoinstvo, 1990 June
    - Iuige igilik, 1992 September
    - Izvestiia, 1994-1995, 1997 January 22
    - Komsomol'skaia pravda, 1995 August-September
    - Lezginskiĭ vestnik, 1992, 1994
    - Limonka, 1995 July
    - Literaturnaia gazeta, 1993 June 16
    - Moskovskiĭ komsomolets, 1997 January 15
    - Musul'manskiĭ vestnik, 1995 August
    - Nezavisimaia gazeta, 1995 June 21, 1997 January
    - Novaia gazeta, 1997 January 20
    - Patriot, 1995 July
    - Pravda Zhirinovskogo, 1994-1995
    - Rossiia, 1994 November 30
    - Rossiĭskaia gazeta, 1995 February-December
    - Rossiĭskie vesti, 1995 September 14, 1996 June 11
    - Segodnia, 1994 January 5
    - Severnyĭ Kavkaz, 1993 July - 1997 January
    - Sovetskaia Rossiia, 1997 January 14
    - Stanitsa, 1992 January and March
    - Tatarskie kraia, 1996 May
    - Terskie vedomosti, 1996 March-April
    - Terskiĭ kazak, 1992
    - Za SSSR, 1995
    - Zavtra, 1994 December - 1997 January
    - Zhenshchiny za mir v svoem otechestve, 1996 June
- Oversize File, 1990 (Box 45)
  - Poster, "Demokraticheskaia Rossiia,", 1990 January 20